Let's go.
Chapter 7 choosing your destination with points of interest.
This is probably the biggest difference between all GPS systems ya they may have a couple of extra features that another one won't have but the biggest thing is point of interest.
Tomtom and Garmin and other types have the most of points of interest.
What a point of interest is if you are looking for restaurants or a park you simple type that in.
So in this case again the tomtom 1 we are going to do a search of point of interest.
Simply click the screen once, we are going to go to navigate to, click points of interest.
Now it is asking if we want a point of interest that is close to us, in the same city, near my home, along our route or any other destination.
So we are going to say a point of interest that is just near us.
Now it is asking what kind of point of interest do we want?
Do we want a category a specific category, a restaurant, a shopping center, or company names?
We would pick a restaurant and just like that we have all the places that are remotely close to us.
So I want to pick let's see we can scroll down.
I'm in the mood for subway so I click subway.
It ask me again if I need to be there in a specific time?
We are just going to click no on that, plans the route, pretty short route, 13 minutes and about 4.4 miles.
Click done that is it we are ready to navigate to subway.